<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CISIS 3175 Lab 4</string>
    <string name="main_fragment_text">One of the 4 fragments here:\n\nMainFragment when app is launched;\n\nThen the fragment for the corresponding button.</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="vancouver_facts">Vancouver is renowned for its breathtaking blend of urban sophistication and natural beauty. Nestled between the Pacific Ocean and majestic mountains, it offers world-class amenities alongside outdoor adventures. Its vibrant arts scene, diverse communities, and commitment to environmental sustainability make Vancouver a dynamic place to live and visit. Consistently ranked among the most livable cities, Vancouver attracts people from around the globe, who are drawn to its high quality of life, rich cultural tapestry, and stunning landscapes.</string>
    <string name="richmond_facts">
        Richmond is a culturally diverse and geographically unique community centrally located on Canada’s West Coast, in Metro Vancouver. The City is 20 minutes from downtown Vancouver, and 25 minutes from the US border and is the location of Vancouver International Airport (YVR). Richmond has a population of 220,000 people and is a unique island city, ideally located in the heart of the Greater Vancouver Region. Richmond is a culturally diverse and geographically unique community centrally located on Canada’s West Coast, in Metro Vancouver. The City is 20 minutes from downtown Vancouver, and 25 minutes from the US border and is the location of Vancouver International Airport (YVR). Richmond has a population of 220,000 people and is a unique island city, ideally located in the heart of the Greater Vancouver Region.
    </string>
    <string name="surrey_facts">
        Surrey is a city in the province of British Columbia, Canada, located south of the Fraser River and north of the Canada–United States border. It is a member municipality of the Metro Vancouver regional district and metropolitan area. Mainly a suburban city, Surrey is the provinces second-largest by population after Vancouver and the third-largest by area after Abbotsford and Prince George. Surrey is a city in the province of British Columbia, Canada, located south of the Fraser River and north of the Canada–United States border. It is a member municipality of the Metro Vancouver regional district and metropolitan area. Mainly a suburban city, Surrey is the province \'s second-largest by population after Vancouver and the third-largest by area after Abbotsford and Prince George.
    </string>
    <string name="bc_facts">
        British Columbia is the westernmost province of Canada, located between the Pacific Ocean and the Rocky Mountains. With an estimated population of 5.1 million as of 2020, it is Canada\'s third-most populous province. The capital of British Columbia is Victoria, the fifteenth-largest metropolitan region in Canada, named for Queen Victoria, who ruled during the creation of the original colonies. The largest city is Vancouver, the third-largest metropolitan area in Canada, the largest in Western Canada, and the second-largest in the Pacific Northwest. In October 2013, British Columbia had an estimated population of 4,606,371 (about 2.5 million of whom were in Greater Vancouver).
    </string>
</resources>